## LAIS ZAGATI

# **Entry-level Software Developer**

laisviana97@gmail.com / +353 892149883 / Dublin, Ireland / LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/laisv/

## **Executive Summary**

Entry-level Junior software developer, currently enrolled in a Diploma in Full stack software development with code Institute. Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python. Have had exposure to project management, object-oriented programming, and testing. I have professional experience of over 6 years in customer support and logistics. I am eager to gain entry into the tech industry into an exciting team where I can both contribute and develop further in my tech career!

#### **Education**

Jan 2024 - Present Diploma in Software Development

**Code Institute** 

Sep 2020 – May 2020 QQI Level 5 Applied Psychology

BFEI - Blackrock Further Education Institute

Jan 2012 – Dec 2015 Faculdades Metropolitanas Unidas - FMU

Bachelor in Tourism and Business Management

#### **Technical Skillset**

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python

Project Management: Trello board, lucid chart, Gannt chart, Agile

Modules Programming and implementation, object-oriented programming, software testing

Additional IT Skills: Microsoft Azure, Microsoft Office, Google Meet, Slack

## **Transferrable Skillset**

- Strong communication skills
- Proactive problem solver
- Team player
- Customer Relationship Management

- Proactive problem solver
- Analytical mindset
- Results focused
- Strong leadership skills

## **Recent projects:**

Airline charges calculator - Had the initiative to develop the airline charges calculator for my team, witnessing
the time-saving benefits it brought to the team at Cencora was gratifying. Creating the airline charges calculator
showcased my ability to streamline processes and improve efficiency through automation. This project,
developed using HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, exemplifies my technical skills and problem-solving capabilities. I am

eager to leverage these experiences to contribute effectively to future projects and initiatives, driving innovation and excellence in the IT industry.

#### **Work Experience**

Jan 2024 – Present **Logistics Coordinator** Cencora, Inc. **Dublin, Ireland** 

- Assisting with cross-referencing invoices received from contractors
- Charges calculating and entering charges in TMS e.g. wait time, recovery fee, airline storage fee, special trucking
- Handling customer queries and escalating serious complaints to management.
- Planning routes and preparing schedules, as well as tracking and reporting progress with shipments.
- Liaising between operations and drivers, as well as collaborating with other departments to optimise transportation services.

May 2021 – Jan 2024

CSR and Logistics Coordinator Colorman Ireland

**Dublin, Ireland** 

- Responsible for providing excellent customer support via phone and email.
- Handling inquiries, resolving complaints, and ensuring smooth logistics operations.
- Coordinate with the production and logistics departments to ensure on-time delivery.
- Maintain detailed and organised records of all sales orders.
- Managing documentation to ensure compliance with associated regulations.

#### Courses

- Zero To Mastery Academy (Udemy) Complete Python Developer (Jan 2024)
- Zero To Mastery Academy Complete (Udemy) Complete Web Developer (Nov 2023)

#### **Interests/Additional Information**

- Participation in Tech Meetups (e.g. Empowering Women in Tech, React & MongoDB Dublin Meetup).
- Lattend regular networking events (e.g. Women in Technology Networking, Women in Tech Dublin, GDG Dublin Events).
  - I spend plenty of time watching YouTube tutorials on programming.
  - I enjoy doing coding challenges online.
  - I speak fluent English and native Portuguese.
  - Learning and gaining useful skills through reading, courses and networking meet-ups.
  - I am a challenge-seeker and that is what dragged me to the Tech world.